Although this is a temple…
雖然我們這裡是寺廟…
Let the Christmas party…
但是 聖誕派對…
Begin!
要開始囉
That's what they say, but on the surface, it's just a year-end party.
說歸說 我們表面上 還是得當成普通的年終聚會才行
WORLDLY DESIRES
(世俗雜念)
(TenPuru -No one can live on loneliness-)
《妙廟美少女》
(Episode 8: Seeing a Turtle is a Good Omen)
(第八話 看見烏龜有好兆頭)
Today is an excellent day to express my gratitude for everyone's daily kindness!
今天是報答大家 平日恩情的大好機會
I, Akagami, will be the first to serve the most delicious food.
首先 就請他們享用 我特別準備的美味料理
Then,
然後
I'll give Miss Yuzuki, who has been very nice to me,
再把我秘密準備的禮物
the gift I've been preparing in secret.
獻給對我有大恩的結月小姐
He said it's delicious food.
他說是美味料理耶
It's just vegetables or something anyway, right?
反正應該也是蔬菜之類的吧
Sorry for the wait.
各位久等了
Meat!
是肉
A-A-Akagami!
赤赤赤赤神
Where did you get so much meat?
這些肉是哪來的呀
I have some connections from my previous job,
我有以前打工時的門路
so I get some for today.
所以今天就特別準備了一些
Please marry me, Akagami.
請和我結婚 赤神哥哥
That would be a great honor.
那可真是我的榮幸
When you grow up…
那我們就等妳長大後再說吧
Akagami, stop it!
赤神 你別說了
Kurage will take it seriously, stop it!
海月是認真的 你別再說了
So everyone…
那麼各位…
Let's eat.
我開動啦
Kurage, what are you doing?
海月 妳幹嘛啦
Eat slowly.
大家慢慢吃吧
We're all full,
既然我們都吃飽了
so it's time to exchange gifts.
那我們差不多該交換禮物了
Yes.
好
It's time. I want to express my gratitude to Miss Yuzuki.
來了 我要向結月小姐表達感謝之意
Miss Yuzuki, what are you doing?
結月小姐 妳這是在做什麼
I'm preparing for the gift exchange.
我在為交換禮物做準備哦
It's more fun to pull this string and get someone else's gift.
只要這樣拉繩子 就可以抽到禮物 不曉得會抽到誰的 真是令人期待呢
No way!
完蛋了
Is the gift exchange random?
交換禮物竟然是隨機的形式嗎
After all, it's my first time attending this party.
畢竟我是第一次參加這個聚會
I thought carefully about everyone's gift.
所以大家的禮物我都單獨想好了
Is there anything I can do?
有什麼辦法嗎
Everyone, tie your gifts.
大家 都把禮物綁好繩子吧
TIE IT TIGHT
(綁緊)
Huh?
咦
Mia, the concept of "I am the gift" doesn't exist in traditional Japanese culture.
米亞 日本的傳統裡 可沒有把自己當禮物這一條哦
What did you say?
妳說什麼
TIE IT TIGHT
(綁緊)
What are you doing?
你又在做什麼呢
As a gift, whoever draws me can choose their favorite organ.
抽到我的人可以挑選 自己喜歡的器官作為禮物
WORTH ABOUT 5 MILLION It's scary. Who would want it?
(差不多值500萬) 好可怕 誰想要啊
So what should I do?
那我該怎麼辦
Me too.
還有我
You didn't prepare a gift? You're hopeless.
你們沒準備好禮物嗎 真拿你們沒辦法
AT YOUR COMMAND COUPON, AKAGAMI Use this as a gift.
(聽您吩咐券 赤神) 你們就拿這個當禮物吧
VALID FOR ONE DAY, EXPIRY ONE YEAR -So that's how it is! -I see!
(一天之內 有效期限一年) -原來還有這招-原來如此
Is everyone ready with their strings?
大家 都有拿到繩子了吧
Yes!
嗯
So one, two.
那麼 一二…
-It's gloves. -Ah, those are from me.
-是手套 -啊 那是我送的
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
-謝謝妳 -不客氣
AT YOUR COMMAND But I'm more interested in Akagami's gift.
(聽您吩咐) 可是我更想要赤神哥哥的禮物
What do you want Akagami to do?
妳想讓赤神幹什麼啊
Tsukuyo, what did you draw?
我順便問一下 月夜 妳抽到的是什麼呢
A little puppet?
這是木芥子嗎
That's from me!
那是我送的
Ah, thanks.
啊 謝謝妳
It seems like an…
好像呀…
Buzz, buzz, buzz.
(嗡嗡嗡)
Sis Yuzuki, something's wrong with this puppet!
結月姐 這個木芥子不對勁
It's my turn to open the gift.
接下來換我開禮物囉
Sis Yuzuki!
結月姐
MARRIAGE REGISTRATION FORM, AOBA KURAGE A piece of paper?
(結婚登記表 蒼葉海月) 是紙嗎
I originally wanted Akagami to accept this.
我本來是想讓赤神哥哥收下這個的
Kurage, let's have a family meeting later.
海月 妳待會過來 跟我開一下家庭會議
CAN AGREE TO ANY ONE CONDITION COUPON, VALID FOR ONE YEAR, AKAGAMI I got my own one.
(可答應任意一個條件券 有效期限一年 赤神) 我抽到的是自己的耶
Me too.
我也是
Oh, same here.
哎呀 我也一樣
TEMPTATION OF NIRVANA Akagami, would you like to exchange with me?
赤神
What is this?
這是…
It's Mia's erotic photo CD.
這是米亞的色情照片光碟哦
Kagura!
神樂
HEHEHEHE When did you take these all?
(呵呵呵呵) 妳什麼時候拍的呀
This must be a joke.
再怎麼說都是開玩笑的吧
Akagami wouldn't watch it.
何況赤神也不會看…
GULP
(吞口水)
Give me that.
給我交出來
But…
但是…
-Give me that. -Alright.
-交出來 -噫 遵命
What Yuzuki said was true, I was joking.
結月說的沒錯 我是開玩笑的
The real gift is this.
真正的禮物是這個
What is that?
那是什麼
LUNAR CLOUDS' HOTSPRING, FREE ADMISSION TICKET A free stay ticket for a hot spring inn.
(月叢雲之湯 免費入場券) 是溫泉旅館的免費入住券
They are open all year round.
他們是全年無休
Operating 24 hours a day.
24小時營業的哦
And it's very close to us.
而且離我們也很近
How can there be such a miraculous inn?
怎麼會有這種奇蹟般的旅館啊
Everyone gets one.
所有人都有份哦
Let's go to the hot spring later!
我們等一下一起去泡溫泉吧
Thank you so much, Kagura.
真是太感謝妳了 神樂
No problem.
沒事沒事
I've also been fortunate to receive your care on regular occasions.
我平時也承蒙各位的照顧了
Please do not mind.
請各位不要在意
Hey, guys there's a cake waiting for you at the end.
各位 這裡還有用來收尾的蛋糕哦
Christmas is the best!
聖誕節 最棒了
Thank you for accompanying me to worship Buddha.
謝謝你陪我供奉主祀神
It's a small matter.
小事一樁啦
This is my first time having such a happy Christmas.
我還是第一次過這麼開心的聖誕節
That's great.
那可真是太好了
Everyone celebrates Christmas like this every year, right?
你們每年都是這麼過聖誕節的嗎
Such scenes are rare.
並沒有這一回事哦
Everyone hasn't been
自從我父親離開
this pleased in a long time,
我母親去了總寺院以後
since my father left and my mother went to the head temple.
大家就再也沒有像現在這麼開心過了
But the only reason we can smile again
但是 我們之所以能重獲笑容
is because you came here, Akagami.
都是因為赤神你來到了這裡
It's all thanks to you, Akagami.
這一定 都是多虧了你
Miss Yuzuki.
結月小姐…
Thank you.
我很感謝你唷
Um…
那個…
So…
所以呢…
Now is a rare opportunity!
現在就是千載難逢的機會
-This is your Christmas present.
-這是給你的聖誕禮物 -這是給妳的聖誕禮物
Huh?
咦
-Akagami, you too? -Miss Yuzuki, you too?
-赤神也要送我嗎 -結月小姐妳也是嗎
Can I open it?
我可以打開嗎
I'll open mine too.
那我也要
Is this the one you got from Mary's shop?
這不就是真梨學姊那裡的…
Handmade prayer beads?
佛珠的體驗製作活動嗎
So we went there at separate times.
也就是說 我們兩個錯開了時間 先後去了那裡嗎
What a coincidence!
真是巧呢
That's why Mary always smirks at me.
(親手製作？呵呵) 難怪真梨學姊會一直對我笑嘻嘻的
Let's exchange then, thank you.
那我們交換一下吧 謝謝你
Yes, thank you very much.
好 謝謝妳
Exchange prayer beads?
交換…佛珠…
After all, in a Buddhist wedding,
畢竟佛教的婚禮上
prayer beads are exchanged rather than rings.
交換的不是戒指而是佛珠哦
Um…
那個…
Why are you all here?
你們怎麼在這啊
Kiki, w-where did you go?
嬉嬉姐 妳 妳去哪啦
The Christmas party is over.
聖誕派對已經結束了哦
There was an issue with your ordaining ceremony, Yuzuki.
結月妳的得度儀式出問題了
Issue?
什麼問題
As I thought, with my skills…
憑我的技術果然還是…
No, it's a problem with the location.
不 是地點的問題
The ceremony will be held in the main hall
儀式會在得度者所修行的寺廟進行
of the temple where the practitioner resides.
也就是這所寺廟的正殿
Many prominent members of our sect will attend the ceremony.
舉行儀式時本宗派的 很多大人物也會到場
It's also a sort of inspection
但是舉行儀式的寺廟
of the temple where the ceremony is taking place.
在另一方面上 也要進行視察才行
The internal meeting may be called off
根據視察的結果
based on the results of the inspection.
法類會議也有可能作廢
But…
但是呀…
TAPE
(膠帶)
To renovate the major Buddha statue, we don't have enough…
我們沒有修繕主祀神的…
Money!
預算呀
KEY BATTLE (TenPuru -No one can live on loneliness-)
(關鍵一役)
This is the inn.
就是這家旅館了
You two.
你們兩個
You will cross the bridge when you get to it.
反正船到橋頭自然直啦
Just enjoy it for now.
我們現在就先好好享受吧
Don't worry about money.
大家不用擔心錢的問題哦
This is a completely free stay voucher.
因為這是完全免費的入住券
Is that so?
真的嗎
We can stay for one night.
我們還可以住一晚哦
I-Is that so?
真 真的嗎
MIXED BATH, FAMILY BATH
(含混浴 家庭浴池)
Welcome!
歡迎光臨
Are you greeting us on your knees?
居然是跪著出來迎接嗎
It's all your illusion.
這都是你的錯覺啦
SOBBING
(抽泣)
-Why is the person who appears to be the boss sobbing? -It's all your illusion.
-那個像是老闆的人為什麼在… -都是你的錯覺啦
Alright, everyone.
好了各位
You can have a soak bath
你們從櫃檯領取毛巾後
as soon as you obtain your towels from the front desk.
就可以馬上去泡澡了哦
Okay.
好
Ah, is this the entrance?
啊 這裡就是入口嗎
I can't remember the last time I took a hot--
我上次泡溫泉是什麼時候了…
What is that?
那是什麼
FOR LORD AKAGAMI ONLY
(赤神大人專用)
Should I go this way?
我走的是這邊嗎
There's even a welcome drink.
竟然還有迎賓飲料
Thank you so much.
太謝謝啦
How exciting.
這飲料喝起來好刺激啊
Then I'll take my leave. Huh?
那我就先告辭了 咦
I'm sorry.
抱歉了…
THREE DAYS OF GREAT EXPERIENCES, FUNCTIONAL BEVERAGES
(三天超絕體驗 機能性飲料)
It's okay, Sis Yuzuki.
沒關係啦 結月姐
Let me take a look too.
讓我也看看吧
Please.
求妳了
I'll only look once.
我就只看一次
Good grief.
真是的…
Only once, okay?
只可以看一次哦
FORCE, DRUM UP Humph.
(用力鼓起) 哼
Sis Yuzuki looks so cute when she's exerting herself.
結月姐用力的樣子也好可愛
How does such a small arm generate such extraordinary strength?
這麼纖細的手臂 是怎麼用出那種怪力的呀
Don't call it extraordinary strength.
不要說怪力啦
If you chop more wood, you'll build muscle.
多劈柴就會長肌肉哦
Will Yuzuki become a muscle girl?
結月會變成肌肉女嗎
Should I also start building muscles?
我是不是也要長長肌肉了
Your chest will also get bigger.
胸也會變大哦
Kurage, watch your words.
海月 注意妳的發言
Also, if it gets any bigger, it might be a bit…
而且再長大的話 我會覺得有點…
SMILE
(微笑)
Then give me your breasts.
那就把妳的給我吧
Give me!
給我吧
OUCH It will be pulled out!
(疼疼疼) 要被妳拔走啦
Alright, stop fooling around.
好了好了 你們別鬧了
What a beautiful hot spring!
好漂亮的溫泉呀
Amazing. Isn't this a private booking? Great.
好厲害 我們包場了耶 太好了
This place is so beautiful.
這裡真漂亮呀
Indeed, it's very beautiful.
確實很漂亮
What happened?
怎麼了
Mia is really beautiful.
米亞真是個美女呀
You appear to be an entirely different person when you let your hair down.
妳把頭髮放下來後 整個人感覺都不一樣了呢
T-Thank you for the compliment.
謝 謝謝誇獎
You all have Akagami's favorite body.
各位也一樣有赤神喜歡的好身材
Thanks for the compliment.
謝謝誇獎…
However, it still can't compare to that person.
不過嘛 我們還是比不過那個人
What a wonderful hot spring.
好棒的溫泉
How does she keep that figure when she's typically so lazy?
平時明明那麼好吃懶做 為什麼她還能保持那種身材…
Master, you're amazing.
師父妳好厲害
BUSTY AND BOUNCY Mia, you're about the same.
(彈性十足) 米亞妳也不遑多讓嘛
Ma-Master!
師 師父
Even as a woman, I think you have a very attractive body.
就算我是女性 對我而言 妳也有著充滿魅力的身體啊
That's not okay, not okay.
不行呀不行呀
BUSTY AND BOUNCY You can't go down the wrong path.
(彈性十足) 我可不能走上邪路呀
Alright, alright!
好了好了
Stop fooling around and soak in the bath!
妳們別鬧了 趕快來泡澡吧
You'll catch a cold!
會感冒的
By the way, where did Kagura go?
對了 神樂去哪裡了
She constantly takes her time changing clothing.
她換衣服的時間本來就很長了
Speaking of Kagura,
對了 說到神樂
she's always holding a camera.
她總是拿著照相機
What has she been taking pictures of?
她都拍了些什麼呀
It's probably something naughty.
恐怕是色色的…
Aren't you curious about why she came to the temple?
妳不好奇她來寺廟的原因嗎
After all, we don't usually ask about reasons for ordination.
畢竟我們從來不過問出家的理由呢
She has always been by my side.
她一直都陪在我身邊
It has been this way since elementary school.
從小學開始就一直是這樣了
MIA When I was lonely and troubled,
-米亞 -我被孤立而煩惱的時候
THERE'S A TENT HERE when I ran away from home after a fight with my parents,
-這裡有帳篷呀 -我和父母吵架離家出走的時候
and when I moved to Japan,
還有我來日本的時候
she naturally followed me.
她也理所當然地跟過來了
Speaking of which,
說起來
Mia was very honest at first.
一開始的時候 米亞看起來非常老實呢
I was really nervous when I first came.
畢竟我剛來的時候很緊張嘛
Now you talk more than before.
妳現在比之前更愛說話了呢
Kagura hardly ever talks about herself.
神樂幾乎不怎麼談論自己的事情呢
Is she secretive or something?
她是保密主義之類的嗎
It's true that I don't know much about her.
她確實有很多連我都不了解的地方
But,
但是就我所知
as far as I am aware,
我可以斷定
Kagura will never betray me.
神樂是絕對不會背叛我的
She is my best friend.
她是我最好的朋友
Miss Mia. That's a lovely story.
米亞小姐…真是一段佳話
So why is everyone in Akagami's private bath?
所以為什麼 大家都在赤神專用浴池裡呢
I was startled and hid reflexively.
我剛才嚇了一跳 害我下意識就躲了起來
Now I look like a peeping tom!
怎麼看我都像是偷窺狂了
But I am too energetic now,
而且我現在的精力還超級旺盛
I can't get out.
害我想出也出不去
Kiki, am I also attractive?
嬉嬉姐 我也有魅力嗎
Uh… hmm.
呃…嗯
I need to slip out quietly.
我得悄悄地溜出去…
HEHE
嘻嘻
I have been found out!
我被發現了
STARING
盯
It's over.
完了…
Huh?
咦
Sorry for being late.
抱歉 我來晚了
Could Miss Kagura
難道說神樂小姐
have seen right through everything?
已經看透一切了嗎
She's a living Buddha.
她簡直就是活菩薩…
Now is the time.
我得趁現在…
By the way, everyone,
對了各位
what would you do
如果赤神現在在偷窺
if Akagami was peeping right now?
你們會怎麼做呢
-Then I'll also peep. -Of course, I'd get angry.
-那我也要去偷窺… -當然是會生氣了
Huh?
咦
Right?
對吧
After all, this is an illegal act.
畢竟這可是違法行為
It calls into question his integrity.
的確會讓人懷疑他的人品
It's an abomination that tramples on people's trust.
而且也是踐踏他人信任的惡行呢
He must be expelled from the temple.
他必然是會被驅逐出寺廟的吧
Indeed so!
確實如此
But we need to talk to him first.
但是 我們還是得先 好好和他談一談呢
After all, it is Akagami, so perhaps he has something difficult to say?
畢竟是赤神嘛 也許他有什麼難言之隱呢
Right.
沒錯
Kagura, you still don't know Akagami well.
神樂 妳還真不了解赤神呢
But it's still very embarrassing, I would probably get angry at him.
不過我還是會羞恥 所以我應該會對他發火吧
Impossibly stupid, Akagami Akemitsu!
你可真是愚不可及 赤神明光
Everyone trusted me,
大家明明如此信賴我
but for a brief moment, I doubted everyone!
我剛才卻還有一瞬間懷疑了大家
Let's go out with a straight face.
我就堂堂正正地走出去吧
Everyone will surely understand me!
大家一定會理解我的
You all really have
各位真是和赤神
a special bond with Akagami.
都有著特別的感情呢
There's nothing special about it.
也沒什麼特別的吧
A lot has happened.
是啊 畢竟發生了很多事嘛
Very special indeed!
很特別哦
All are beautiful things.
的確是盡發生些美事呢
Right?
對吧
Everyone!
大家
Akagami is here.
赤神在此
Ahhhhhh!
呀啊啊啊
Seeing a turtle at the end of the year is a good omen.
到了年關 看見烏龜就會有好兆頭
A turtle?
有龜嗎
Is that so?
是這樣嗎
So this was an unfortunate accident.
所以這是一場不幸的事故
Hmm.
嗯…
But it's also true that you've been in hiding for a while.
但是你暫時躲了起來也是事實
Alright, we should forgive him now.
好了 你們差不多饒了他吧
After all, he came out on his own.
畢竟他是自己走出來的
Indeed, he did the right thing in this regard.
這一點他確實做得很對
And…
而且…
SQUIRMING That was indeed very outstanding.
(扭來扭去) 那確實非常雄偉呢
It seems to be more robust than before.
好像比之前更雄壯了…
Very manly.
非常有男子氣概
T-Thank you.
多 多謝
Should we go back now?
各位 我們差不多該回去了吧
Why not stay for the night?
我們不住一晚嗎
The temple can't be left unattended all the time.
寺裡不能一直沒人呀
Can I stay?
我可以留下來嗎
I want to enjoy the hot spring more.
我還想再好好泡泡溫泉
Then I'll stay too! I want to explore the inn more!
那我也留下來 我還想再參觀旅館
Hmm, okay.
嗯 可以唷
I should go back too.
那麼 我也該回去了
Akagami, you'd better
赤神
take another bath.
我覺得你也重新泡個澡會比較好哦
No, I should go back to the temple.
不了 我該回寺裡去了
Are you planning to go back with your lower half in that state?
你打算下半身保持那樣回去嗎
I'll stay!
我留下來
The indoor bath is also nice.
室內浴池也不錯嘛
But
但是這個
why isn't it going down?
為什麼完全軟不下來啊
Do you want me to help you with that?
要我幫你軟下來嗎
Hmm, please…
嗯嗯 拜託了…
Miss Kagura? W-W-Why are you here?
神樂小姐 妳妳妳為什麼在這裡
-I'll go out right now! -Don't try to escape.
-我這就出去 -休想逃走
It's simple to calm you down.
讓你冷靜下來是很簡單的哦
Let me guide you to enlightenment.
就讓我來指引你走上開悟的境界吧
Give up your resistance.
放棄抵抗吧
Shatter the distractions!
看我粉碎雜念
You really can endure.
你還真是能忍啊
I've thought of a lot of strategies
為了讓你輸給自己的雜念而搞砸一切
to get you to lose yourself in your distractions.
我可是想了不少策略的
What?
啥
Bribing the hot spring inn to set a trap.
比方說我買通了旅館 並在溫泉設下圈套
Giving you an aphrodisiac while tricking you into thinking it was a welcome drink.
還有讓你把春藥誤以為是迎賓飲料 騙你喝下去
So that's what caused all this!
原來我是被下藥了嗎
Now even my beauty tricks don't work, it's really troublesome.
現在連我的美人計也沒什麼效果 真是很困擾啊
Wait a minute! Why are you doing this?
等一下 妳為什麼要做這些事
To exterminate pests.
當然驅除害蟲啊
Huh?
什麼
I beg you, Akagami.
算我求你了 赤神
Can you leave Mikazuki Temple?
你可以離開三日月寺嗎
I want to implement my plan.
我要實現我的計劃
You are a stumbling block in the process.
而你卻是過程中的一個絆腳石
Plan?
什麼計劃
That's why I came to Japan.
我就是為此來到日本的
For my Lustful Queen Raising Plan.
為了我的好色女王養成計劃
The plan is for Mia
(好色女王養成計劃) 計劃內容是讓米亞在日本的期間
INTERNATIONAL EXCHANGE AT NIGHT to have sex intercourse sessions
(夜間國際交流) 至少和一百名男性
with at least a hundred men during her stay in Japan.
進行性愛實習課程
W-What are you talking about?
妳 妳在說什麼啊
Miss Mia
米亞小姐正是
is the Christoph family's next clan leader.
下一任克莉絲多夫家的當家
Miss Kagura?
神樂小姐
She is destined to become
她必須得成為能出色地領導
a prominent leader of the erotic family…
好色家族的女中豪傑…
Miss Kagura, that--
神樂小姐 那個
Didn't you notice I hadn't finished speaking?
你真是不解風情 我話都還沒說完呢
I'm sorry. My mind's not working.
抱歉 我腦子轉不過來了
I thought this plan would go smoothly,
我本以為這個計劃可以順利進行
but Miss Mia and you have reached
但沒想到米亞小姐竟和你
an agreement on removing distractions.
在封印雜念的方面達成了共識
W-Wait a minute!
等 等一下
Miss Mia is here because she despises her family's situation.
米亞小姐是因為厭惡家裡的情況…
That's right.
沒錯哦
Why did you do it when you knew?
妳明明知道 為什麼還…
Why do you think it is?
你覺得是為什麼呢
What exactly do you think
你覺得參與這個計劃的我
I am involved in this plan?
究竟是什麼人呢
Miss Kagura, have you always had
神樂小姐 妳難道一直對米亞小姐…
traitorous intentions…
有著背叛的…
toward Miss Mia?
心嗎
My friend… My best friend and Akagami!
我的朋友…最好的朋友和赤神居然…
Should I join too?
我是不是也該插一腳
One, two, three.
一 二 三
Fall asleep.
睡倒
Miss Mia!
米亞小姐
One, two, three.
一 二 三
Kagura… falls asleep.
神樂…睡倒
The first thing I learned was how to smile.
我最初學到的是如何微笑
My family name is Baldwin.
我的家族名是鮑德溫
Baldwin is a branch of the Christoph family.
鮑德溫家 是克莉絲多夫家的旁系家族
We do a lot of behind-the-scenes work
我們替陽光下的克莉絲多夫家
for the Christoph family who get all the credit.
承擔了很多陰影中的工作
Do you understand?
你能理解嗎
Not really.
我不是很理解…
Traitorous?
什麼背不背叛的
I was a loyal dog to the Christoph family
我出生在鮑德溫家
since the day I was born into the Baldwin family.
我打從一開始就只是 克莉絲多夫家的忠犬
Then why don't you do this?
那妳要不要這麼做呢
It's not too late for you and Ms. Mia
現在開始還不算太遲
to fight back against the family's obstacles.
妳可以和米亞小姐 一起向家族的枷鎖發起反抗
You are really an interesting person.
你果然是個有趣的人呢
So, why are you
赤神 你又為什麼
working as a temple attendant at Mikazuki Temple, Akagami?
會在三日月寺做寺務員呢
It's because I have debts.
那是因為我有欠債…
What are you going to do after you pay off your debts?
那你還清你欠的債之後呢
What will you do then?
你又要去做什麼
After paying off…
還清以後…
And stay until I became abbot?
你就這樣一直做到住持嗎
Or leave the temple to find a job?
還是離開寺廟去找工作呢
In the end, why did you come to Mikazuki Temple?
說到底 你來到三日月寺的原因 究竟是什麼呢
It's because I've always been troubled by the Akagami family's bloodline.
是因為…我一直深受 赤神家血脈的困擾
I want to overcome distractions.
所以我想克服雜念…
Oh my.
哎呀
So you escaped from home, didn't you?
也就是說你從家裡逃出來了
Right?
對不對
Whether it's Mia or you,
米亞也好 你也好
you're all just fleeing.
都只是在逃避罷了
Miss Yuzuki bravely faced her family,
結月小姐可是鼓起勇氣直面家族了呢
isn't that very rude of you?
你們這樣豈不是很失禮嗎
Um…
這個…
Let's make a deal, Akagami.
我們來做個交易吧 赤神
A deal?
什麼交易
I will pay off all your debts,
你欠的債由我來幫你還清
and I'll cover the cost of the Buddha's repairs.
主祀神的修繕費也由我來出
Why would you do this?
妳為什麼要做這種事…
As long as you leave,
只要赤神你願意離開
Mikazuki Temple can easily overcome the difficulties.
三日月寺就可以輕鬆度過難關
Please consider it seriously.
請你好好考慮一下吧
Pound and beat.
(下一話 打年糕也很色色呢) 捶捶打打
Soft and puffy.
軟軟呼呼
Naked?
光溜溜